distributorcentral.com 2010-08-21

# 

The DistributorCentral.com website (the “Site”) is owned and operated by DistributorCental, LLC, a Kansas
limited liability company (“DistributorCentral” “we” or “us”), and this Privacy Policy governs the manner in
which DistributorCentral collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users of the Site
(each, a “User”) and the services provided thereon (the “Services”). DistributorCentral reserves the right, at
our discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check
this Privacy Policy periodically for changes. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes
to these terms will mean you accept those changes.
Privacy
DistributorCentral is committed to safeguarding the information Users entrust to us and believes every User
should know how we utilize the information collected from the Site.
The Information We Collect
DistributorCentral may collect personally identifiable information from Users in a variety of ways.
Personally identifiable information may include: (i) contact data (such as a User’s name, telephone number,
mailing and e-mail addresses); (ii) financial data (such as a User’s account or credit card number); (iii)
pricing, sales, product and order information; and (iv) demographic data (such as a User’s zip code, age and
income). If you communicate with us by e-mail or otherwise complete online applications, forms, surveys or
orders, any information provided in such communication may be collected by us. We may also collect
information about how Users use the Site, for example, by tracking the number of unique views received by
the pages of the Site, or the domains from which Users originate. We may also use “cookies” to track how
Users use our Site. A cookie is a piece of software that a Web server can store on the User’s computer to
identify the User should they visit the Site again. While not all of the information that we collect from Users
is personally identifiable, it may be associated with personally identifiable information that Users provide us
through the Site.
How We Use Information
DistributorCentral will not share any User’s personally identifiable information with any third party, with
any other User or with any affiliate or business partner of DistributorCentral, without such User’s prior
consent. We may, however, use a User’s personally identifiable information collected through the Site to
contact such User from time to time via email, mail and/or telephone regarding the Site and the Services.
Additionally, each User agrees that we may disclose personally identifiable information to any third party in
the good faith belief that such action is reasonably necessary: (a) to comply with any applicable law, rule,
regulation or legal process; (b) to enforce any term of this Privacy Policy or the Terms of Use of the Site;
(c) to respond to claims that the User is engaged in activities that violate the rights of third parties; or (d) to
protect the rights or interests of DistributorCentral or any third party; provided, however, that nothing in this
Privacy Policy shall impose a duty on DistributorCentral to make any such disclosures. User further
acknowledges and agrees that technical processing of certain personally identifiable information is and may
be required: (a) to provide the Services to such User; or (b) to conform to the technical requirements of
connecting networks or other similar technical requirements. User also acknowledges and agrees that we
may access User’s information as necessary to identify or resolve technical problems or respond to
complaints about the Site or the Services. We may also use or disclose to potential partners any aggregate,
anonymous data based on information collected from Users. Finally, we may transfer information collected
from Users in connection with a sale of our business or assets to any third party.
Maintenance of Information
Information about Users that is maintained on our system is protected using industry standard
security measures. However, we cannot guarantee that any User’s information submitted to,
maintained on, or transmitted from our systems will be completely secure.
